Derek Pacula

Full Stack Web Developer

🦞 16094 Fairoaks Ave N Hugo, MN 55038 │ 📞 4023170724 │ 🖂 derek@pacula.me

pacula.dev

Application Web Deveoper with 7+ years of experience with a wide arange of skills including Angular, Vue, Node.JS, SQL Technologies, AWS. Trusted person who has lead serveral projects start to finish, entrusted to listen to client requriements and feedback, and has mentored and helped fellow employees to bring up their skills.

OBJECTIVE

Use my extensive set of web development skills, built in a team environment, to deliver modern UI solutions to projects at hand, and assist in mentoring people with my knolwedge and experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUNE 2016 - CURRENT

Senior Developer | DevOps Engineer

Opti9 (formerly Jelecos)

Formailized and Create CI/CD Pipelines and Infrastrucre as Code and setting up new development tools that team would use

Create inovative solutions to automate and improve development release processes

Lead product demos and workshops to customers, potential customers

Lead on-stie client meetings to understand and articualte project requirement and desires

Responsible for translating business requirements into high quality techincal design and working software

Developing wireframes and task flows based on user needs and translating requirements to create custom, intuitive, and user friendly software

MAY 2012 - JUNE 2016

Mobile Implementations Analyst

Eicon/

Writing requirements for software development to authorization application

Using, configuring, and modifying third party authorization simulators

Creating detailed, client-facing test scripts for sanctioned, department-wide use

Application Maintenance

SKILLS

ANGULAR, VUE	UI / UX DESIGN
JAVASCRIPT, NODE.JS	MYSQL, MICROSOFT SQL SERVER
AWS	.NET MVC

EMPLOYEE SKILLS AND CAREER ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Communication and understanding client requirements

AWS Certified DevOps Professional

Training and mentoring new developers

Two-time employee of the quarter winner at Jelecos

Member of Jelecos Cloud Center of Excellence, an exclusive leadership group

EDUCATION

AUGUST 2011 - DECMBER 2015

Bachelor's of Computer Science

University of Nebraska Omaha